Guide to the Samuel Kravitt Photographs and Other Materials
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Samuel Kravitt photographs and other materials
1940-1950
MS 1923
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
6.5
(13 boxes)
The materials comprise photographs, a photographic negative collection documenting life at Yale during World War II, exhibit files, and biographical information documenting the work of Samuel Kravitt as photographer.
Kravitt, Samuel, 1913-2000
General note
This collection was previously known as the Samuel Kravitt Photographic Negative Collection Documenting Life at Yale during World War II (RU 668).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Boxes 1-8 were transferred from RU 668. Boxes 9-12 are the gift of Marcia U. Kravitt, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Samuel Kravitt was born in New Haven, Connecticut, in 1913. He left high school in 1929, intending to become a pilot. After borrowing a World War I aerial camera, however, he decided on a career in photography. From 1930 to 1931, he served as apprentice to Joseph Stone, a local portrait photographer. In 1932, Kravitt opened his first studio at age 19 in downtown New Haven. In the early 1930s, he was commissioned to document the lifestyle of the Shaker community in Hancock, Massachusetts. He subsequently relocated to New York and was staff photographer for the New York World's Fair Corporation from 1937 to 1939, documenting the construction of the Fair. Kravitt returned to New Haven in 1940, opening a studio in the Yale Record Building. He made a transition from still photography to filmmaking during the 1950s and in 1962 founded Associated Film Consultants, a New York-based independent production company. Kravitt died in 2000.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The materials comprise photographs, a photographic negative collection documenting life at Yale during World War II, exhibit files, and biographical information documenting the work of Samuel Kravitt as photographer.
Photographers; Photography; Kravitt, Samuel, 1913-2000
- Papers
  - Articles
    - Saturday Review of Literature, 1933-1940 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - "Yale in 1943," This Week Magazine, 1943 September 19 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1944 October 29 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Biographical, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Client information, 1933-1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Exhibits
    - Arts council, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Nantucket, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Sixty-five Years Behind the Camera, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Utopia, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Wilton, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Fashion model brochure, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - New Haven television films, Circa 1951 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New York World's Fair, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Press, 1936-2004 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Resettlement Administration, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Yale logo/mascot, 1944, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Photographs
  - Aerials, Circa 1937 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Aerial view of Paris, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Aerial views of New York City area, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Africa, Circa 1962 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Oversize, 1972, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
    - Woman, Undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Airplanes in flight, Undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - American Flagship plane in flight, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Antigua race week, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Awards
    - 1963 Davis and Geck Award, bronze medal, Injuries of the Hands and Face, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 1969 Gold Award, Fashion documentary Qiana-New York-Paris, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Barbados, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Sails drying, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Beach/waterfront, Undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Beyond the Lens: Glimpses of Shaker Life Opening Day, Wilton Historical Society, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Brazil, Undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - British West Indies, Undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Tropical storm, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Call It a Day posters, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Capri, Bay of Naples, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Children, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Construction, unidentified, Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Ecuador, 1974, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Children of the Rainforest, Merck Project, Circa 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Dr. John Walden, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Negatives, including Dr. John Walden, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Fashion, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Oversize, Undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Oversize, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Furniture, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Hands, Undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Handsome Dan, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Kravitt, Sam, on location, Circa 1960s-1970s (Box 10, Folder 14-15)
  - Machinery (unidentified), Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Manhattan aerial shots, Undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Mexico City, bull fighter, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - New Haven, Undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - New York, Undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - City street, Undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - New York World's Fair
    - Advertising models, completed building, Circa 1939 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Aerial contact prints, Circa 1939 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Construction, Circa 1939 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Aerial view, Circa 1939 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Oversize, Circa 1939 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Construction contact prints, Circa 1939 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Construction workers, Circa 1939 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Corporation president and photographers, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Japanese tea ceremony, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Labors of Man Group, George H. Snowden, sculptor, 1939-1940 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Labors of Man Group contact prints, Circa 1939 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Site model, Circa 1939 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "Streets of Paris" billboard, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes a transparency.
  - On board the S.S.Uruguay, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Crew at work, Undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Pan-Am terminal and field, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Paris, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Persian Empire Celebration reception, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Portraits
    - Anamonthota, Dr., Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Brewster, Kingman, Undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Buchanan, George, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Caniff, Milton, autographed, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Cantu, Max, thoracic surgeon at St. Raphael's, Undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Cozza, Carm, Undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - McGinnis, Patrick, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Meeks, Everett, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Morley, Christopher, Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Seymour, Charles, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Tuttle, Emerson, making an etching, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Vine, Ruby, Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Walden, John, Dr., Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Warren, H. E., Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Weaver, Charlie, Undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Oversize, Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Welch, Constance, Circa 1970 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Oversize, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Wright, Richard, Undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Portugal, 1961, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Republican Convention, Philadelphia, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Shaker Village, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Brother making box, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Oversize, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Shipwreck, Cape Vert, Senegal, Undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Oversize, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - South America, Circa 1948 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Still lifes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Three presidents: James R. Angell, James B. Conant, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, Undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Trinidad, Undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Tropics, Undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Unidentified ruins of 1691 building, Undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - West Indies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - World War II, Undated (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Yale buildings
    - Architectural detail
      - Lux et Veritas shield (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Unidentified, Undated (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Bingham Hall: Yale Fence relief, Undated (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Law School architectural details, Undated (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous buildings, Circa 1998 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Oversize, Undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Sterling Memorial Library
      - Details: Aristotle, J.S. Bach, Cristopher Columbus, Da Vinci, Herodatus, Justinian, Undated (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Details: Moses, Shakespeare, Adam Smith, Socrates, Vitruvius, Undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Tower, Undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Strathcona architectural details, Undated (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Yale people, Undated (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Yale ROTC, World War II, Undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Negatives
  - World War II groups (Box 1, Folder 1 - 45)
  - Yale buildings
    - Book & Snake Tomb, 1951 May 24 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Harkness Tower from the Old Campus (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Historical Medical Library (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Pierson Gateway, 1948 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Pierson College, 1948 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Noah Porter Gateway, 1948 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Trumbull College, 1948 May 1 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Yale Organizations (Box 2, Folder 53 - 72)
  - Yale People
    - Day, George P. (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - DeVane, Dean W.C. (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Gill (Captain) (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Haggard, Howard W., M.D. (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Neibuhr, H. Richard (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Phelps, William Lyon (hands) (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Southwick, Dr. Wayne (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Tinker, Prof. C.B. (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Whitridge, Prof. Arnold (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Whitridge, Arnold (hands) (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Winternitz, Dr. Milton (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Yale buildings
    - Berkeley College (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Book & Snake Tomb (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Branford Courtyard (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Branford Courtyard, Harkness (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Calhoun College (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Connecticut Hall (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Dwight Chapel (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Farnam House (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Harkness - front, Old Campus (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Old Campus from Phelps (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Payne Whitney Gym (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Phelps Gateway (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Photo lab of Applied Psychology (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Sage Hall - Yale Forestry (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Old room at Sterling Library (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Sterling Library - exterior (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Sterling Library - interior (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Strathcona Hall (Box 3, Folder 101 - 102)
    - Walter Camp Field (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Wright Hall (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Yale Art Gallery (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Yale Fence (Box 3, Folder 106 - 107)
    - Yale Law School (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Yale Observatory (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Yale University Press (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Bicentennial Buildings (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Sheffield-Sterling-Strathcona Hall (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Yale Law School (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Unidentified (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Campus snow scenes (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Campus scenes (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Campus scenes (Box 3, Folder 115 - 117)
    - Aerial views (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Yale organizations (Box 3, Folder 119 - 142)
  - Yale people
    - Babb, James T. (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Ford, Alan (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Griswold, A.W. (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Handsome Dan (Yale bulldog) (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Montana (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Seymour, Charles (group photos) (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Seymour, Charles (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Seymour, Charles and Ambassador Grew (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Timm, Judd (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Yale faculty
    - Adams, J.C. (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Anderson, R.J. (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - Brouwer, Dirk (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Buck, Allen (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Buck (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Cowgill, G.R. (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Conrad (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Conrad (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Crosby (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Curtiss, Joseph T. (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Day, George P. (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Day, J.P. (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Dudley, Samuel (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Eberhard (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Farnam, Thomas W. (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - French, Robert E. (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Frye, Clements (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Godley, Frederick (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Gulliver, A.G. (Box 3, Folder 170 - 171)
    - Harper, Fowler V. (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Holden, Captain R.A. (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Holden, Reuben (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Huntington, Ellsworth (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Keller, A.G. (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Knollenberg (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Lindsay, H.D. (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - McCandless, Stanley (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - May, Merle (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Meeks, Carroll (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Meeks, (Dean) (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Mienaglos, Frank (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Northrop, F.S.C. (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Peyre, Henri (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Phelps, William Lyon (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - Rotival, Maurice (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Schroeder, J.C. (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Sheldon, Wilmon (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Shulman, Harry (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - Smith, E.D. (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Sturges, W.H. (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Tucker, Luther (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Walker, Charles (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Walker (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Warren, Dean (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Wolfers, Arnold (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Woodruff, Dr. (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Yerkes, Dr. (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Divinity School faculty
    - Archer, Dr. J.C. (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Bainton, Dr. Roland. (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Banner, William (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Bock, Paul J. (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Burrows, Rev. Millar (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Calhoun, Robert L. (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Dinkler, Erich (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Eusden, John D. (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Forman, Charles W. (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Glasse, James D. (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Harthorne, H. (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Hartt, J.N. (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Heins, Norvin J. (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - Kirkland, William H. (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Latourette, K.S. (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Lindbeck, G.A. (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Luccock, H.E. (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - McConnel, Bishop (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Michaelson, Robert (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Morris, R.P. (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Muehl, Ernest (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Napier, B.D. (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Nelson, J.O. (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Niebuhr, Dr. R. (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Niebuhr, Mr. and Mrs. (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - Outler, Albert C. (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Pope, Liston (Box 4, Folder 226 - 227)
    - Pope, Marvin H. (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Rasmussen, Albert T. (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Schubert, Paul (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Shedd, Dr. C.B. (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Smith, Seymour A. (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Underwood, Kenneth (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - Vieth, Paul E. (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - Weigle, Dean L.A. (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - Weigle, Dean Luther (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - Welch, Rev.Claude R. (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - Woodward, Ralph L. (Box 4, Folder 238)
  - Divinity School - buildings and grounds (Box 4, Folder 239)
  - Yale Drama Department faculty
    - Atkinson, Olive (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - Banks, William S. (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Bartlett, Martine (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - Bevan, Frank (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - Brookman, Emanuel (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Browne, Oden (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - Brugge, John Berssen (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - Bullock, Robert (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - Byrle, Cass (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - Cole, E.C. (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Connelly, Mark (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Dace, Wallace (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - [empty folder] (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Diamant, William (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Dunlap, Richard (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Esler, Lemist (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Evans, Marylyn (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Falk, Irving (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Feldman, Joan (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Hailechase, H. (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Helstien, Melvin (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Henry, George (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Izeneur, George C. (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Levandro, L.S. (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - McMullen, Frank (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Marshall, Howard (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - Nagler, Alois (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - Oenslager, Donald (Box 4, Folder 266a)
    - Parker, Oren (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Perlowin, Eugene M. (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Porter, Stephen (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Powell, Addison (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Reveaux, Edward (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Schoenhut, George W. (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Sheridan, Claire (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Sherrill, Elaine (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Sigler, Sarah (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Smith, Boyd (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - Smith, H.K. (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Todd, Robert (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Medical School faculty
    - Bayne-Jones, Stanhope (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Beeson, Dr.Paul B. (Box 4, Folder 280 - 281)
    - Board of Scientific Advisors (Box 4, Folder 282 - 283)
    - Chase, Dr. Robert (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Jane Coffin Childs Foundation (Box 4, Folder 285 - 286)
    - Jane Coffin Childs Fund (Box 4, Folder 287 - 289)
  - Medical School class group (Box 4, Folder 290 - 291)
  - Medical School faculty
    - Glenn, Dr. W.W. (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - Hayes, Dr. M.A. (Box 4, Folder 293)
    - Hayes, Dr. Mark (Box 4, Folder 294)
    - Horstmann, Dr. Dorothy (Box 4, Folder 295 - 296)
    - Lindskog, Dr. G.E. (Box 4, Folder 297)
    - Malinowski (Box 4, Folder 298)
    - Mark, Dr. James (Box 4, Folder 299)
    - Paul, Dr. John R. (Box 4, Folder 300)
    - Shedd, Dr. Donald (Box 4, Folder 301)
    - Snoke, Dr. A.W. (Box 4, Folder 302)
    - Surgical staff - New Haven Hospital (Box 4, Folder 303)
    - Surgical House staff (Box 4, Folder 304)
    - Surgical staff - Yale Medical School (Box 4, Folder 305 - 309)
    - Taylor, Dean Effie (Box 4, Folder 310)
  - Student Life (Box 4, Folder 311 - 326)
    General note
    Error in numbering--There are no materials in folder 335.
  - Yale - War Years (Box 5, Folder 327 - 390)
  - Yale - War Years (Box 6, Folder 391 - 410)
  - Individuals
    - Biff (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - Carroll, Madeline (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - Grosson (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - Hirshberg, Edward (Box 6, Folder 414)
    - Killma, C. (Box 6, Folder 415)
    - King, Mose (Box 6, Folder 416)
    - Kyelinth, Robert (Box 6, Folder 417)
    - Maugham, Somerset (Box 6, Folder 418)
    - Miller, O.D. (Box 6, Folder 419 - 420)
    - Moiragnau, Frank (Box 6, Folder 421)
    - Moriarity, Philip (Box 6, Folder 422)
    - Mosley, Spence (Box 6, Folder 423)
    - Murdock (Box 6, Folder 424)
    - Neal, Witty (Box 6, Folder 425)
    - O'Dell (Box 6, Folder 426)
    - The O'Dells (Box 6, Folder 427)
    - O'Donnell, Eddie (Box 6, Folder 428)
    - Rolph, Red (Box 6, Folder 429)
    - Root, Reggie (Box 6, Folder 430)
    - Seabury, Dr. (Box 6, Folder 431)
    - Woodcock (Box 6, Folder 432)
    - Knight, Douglas (Box 6, Folder 433)
    - Tunnard, Christopher (Box 6, Folder 434)
    - Angell, Dr. James Rowland (Box 6, Folder 435)
    - Hitchcock, Meacham (Box 6, Folder 436)
    - King, Mosey (Box 6, Folder 437)
    - Melnick, Dr. Joseph (Box 6, Folder 438)
    - Southwick, Dr. Wayne (Box 6, Folder 439)
    - Southwick, Mrs. Wayne (Box 6, Folder 440)
  - Yale Football players, 1942-1950 (Box 7, Folder 441 - 634)
  - YAA Football Bus., 1947 October (Box 8, Folder 635 - 667)
  - YAA Coaches, 1942-1949 (Box 8, Folder 668 - 703)
  - Football group pictures and Captains Dinners, 1942-1950 (Box 8, Folder 704 - 720)
  - Crew - individuals, teams, 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 721 - 756)
  - Miscellaneous sports, 1942-1947 (Box 8, Folder 757 - 764)